http://www.nvsi.com/privacypolicy.html

Share with your friends:
Home
SofTutor with Content for:
AutoCAD® (2009 - 2012)
AutoCAD (R14-2008)
MicroStation®Office 2010
SofTutor Training, Support & Collaboration:
Consulting Services
Buy Now!
Contact Us
Our Blog:
Google+: SofTutor
FREE STUFF!
Downloadable Demos:
SofTutor MicroStation 3D
SofTutor MicroStation Adv.
Updates Twitter: @FreeCADTraining
Other SofTutor
v 3 Demos
Second Life Academic ISTE
Sponsored Group:
SofTutorKids.com
Privacy Policy
Last modified: Feb. 6, 2015
At NVSI we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by New Vision Software, Incorporated ("NVSI") or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at
NVSI Privacy
Policy
130 Kainer Ave.
Barrington, IL 60010
USA
Information we collect and how we use it
We
offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an
account or provide any personal information to us, such as NVSI
Search. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect
the following types of information:
Information you provide – When you sign up for a SofTutor OnLine
Account or other NVSI or SofTutor service or promotion that requires registration, we ask
you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an
account password). For certain services, such as our advertising
programs, we also request credit card or other payment account
information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We
may combine the information you submit under your account with
information from other NVSI services or third parties in order to
provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our
services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt
out of combining such information.
Cookies – When you visit NVSI, we
send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of
characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies
your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service,
including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad
selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. NVSI
also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and
publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more
cookies in your browser when you visit a website, including NVSI
sites that use our advertising cookies, and view or click on an ad
supported by NVSI’s advertising services.
Log information – When you access
NVSI services, our servers automatically record information that your
browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol
address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your
request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your
browser.
User communications – When you send
email or other communications to NVSI, we may retain those
communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your
requests and improve our services.
Affiliated NVSI Services on other sites – We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal
information that you provide to those sites may be sent to NVSI in
order to deliver the service. We process such information under this
Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites through which our services are
offered may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to
read their privacy policies.
Plugins – NVSI may make available
third party applications through its services. The information
collected by NVSI when you enable a plugin or other application is
processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the
application or plugin provider is governed by their privacy policies.
Location data – Should NVSI offer
location-enabled learning services, such as NVSI location learning for mobile. If you use
those services, NVSI may receive information about your actual
location (such as GPS signals sent by a mobile device) or information
that can be used to approximate a location (such as a cell ID).
Links – NVSI may present links in a
format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been
followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search
technology, customized content and advertising.
Other sites – This Privacy Policy applies to NVSI services only. We do not
exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that
include NVSI applications, products or services, or links from within
our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or
other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal
information from you.
NVSI only processes personal information for
the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary
privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such
purposes include:
Providing our services, including the display of customized content and advertising;
Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
Ensuring the technical functioning of our network;
Protecting the rights or property of NVSI or our users; and
Developing new services.
You
can find more information about how we process personal information by
referring to the supplementary privacy notices for particular services.
NVSI processes personal information on our servers in the
United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we
process personal information on a server outside your own country. We
may process personal information to provide our own services. In some
cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according
to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.
Choices for personal information
When
you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask
you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a
manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we
will ask for your consent prior to such use.
If we propose to use personal information for any purposes
other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the
specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to
opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We
will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or
in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained
your prior consent.
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but
you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a
cookie is being sent. However, some NVSI features and services may
not function properly if your cookies are disabled.
NVSI uses the google analytics and statcounter cookies to track website usage for analysis to make our website(s) more beneficial for our customers and users.
You
can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in
which case NVSI may not be able to provide those services to you.
Information sharing
NVSI
only shares personal information with other companies or individuals
outside of NVSI in the following limited circumstances:
We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
We
provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or
other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing
personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree
to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance
with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and
security measures.
We have a good faith belief that access, use,
preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary
to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or
enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of
Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c)
detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical
issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety
of NVSI, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
If NVSI becomes involved in a merger,
acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will
ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such
transactions and provide notice before personal information is
transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information,
such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for
example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such
information does not identify you individually.
Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.
Information security
We
take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized
access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of
data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage
and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical
security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where
we store personal data.
We restrict access to personal information to NVSI
employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in
order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals
are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to
discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they
fail to meet these obligations.
Data integrity
NVSI
processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was
collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable
service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage
and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and
process the personal information needed to provide or improve our
services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take
reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is
accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update
or correct their personal information whenever necessary.
Accessing and updating personal information
When
you use NVSI services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with
access to your personal information and either to correct this data if
it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not
otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business
purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the
information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before
processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that
are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate
technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be
extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information
residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise
required. In any case where we provide information access and
correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so
would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have
different procedures to access, correct or delete users’ personal
information. We provide the details for these procedures in the
specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services.
Enforcement
NVSI
regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel
free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy
or NVSI’s treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at
NVSI Privacy
Policy
130 Kainer Ave.
Barrington, IL 60010
USA
When
we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is NVSI’s
policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns.
We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities,
including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints
regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between
NVSI and an individual.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Please
note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not
reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit
consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we
will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes
are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including,
for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).
Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of
the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
If
you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy
Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site
or at
NVSI Privacy
Policy
130 Kainer Ave.
Barrington, IL 60010
USA
SofTutor's unique training method goes beyond classroom training and other teaching, training,
learning or tutorial products by combining hands on video learning system with easy to follow
along examples in the actual product being taught.
Depending on the way you use SofTutor, SofTutor Online Pay-Per-View or the new SofTutor Learning System or SofTutor Learning Player you can follow along and learn by doing in your application or AutoCAD or MicroStation.
Students who use our content will learn AutoCAD or
MicroStation 2D, 3D or Advanced CAD or CADD faster with SofTutor than with other tutorials or even university classes or courses.
SofTutor's instruction is clear and easy to follow, if you're an engineer, architect, designer or manager, SofTutor is for you.
You'll master AutoCAD or MicroStation 2D, 3D or Advanced topics in no time.
SofTutor Online is our web/intranet version that runs in a web browser.
Our new SofTutor Learning System can run locally, on your network, intranet or internet for training, technical support or group collaboration.
If you can make a video, screencast, screen video using snagit, camtasia studio, hypercam, windows media encoder or other tools you can make, modify or customize SofTutor learning products on your own system.
SofTutor works great for software and information technology (IT) training, collaboration and help desks can use it to reduce the time it takes for your users to learn.
MicroStation is a registered trademark of Bentley Systems, Inc.
AutoCAD is a registered trademark of Autodesk, Inc.
1994 - 2012 Copyright New Vision Software, Incorporated. All Rights Reserved.
SofTutor is a registered trademark of New Vision Software, Incorporated.
"the end of the learning curve", "Teacher Inside of ...", Teacher Inside ...", "Teacher Inside of AutoCAD", "Teacher Inside of MicroStation", "Teacher Inside of MS Office", "Teacher inside of Photoshop" are trademarks of New Vision Software, Incorporated. All other trademarks are the property of their respective holders.
NVSI.com respects your privacy click here to review our privacy statement.
